Now, in here we see that many references to black saints:
Hier sehen wir Bezüge zu den Heiligen Schwarzen
St. Benedict the Moor, St. Elesbaan of Axum,
São Benedito, Santo Elesbão,
Our Lady of Sorrows, St. Roch...
Nossa Senhora das Dores, São Roque...
You can notice how in this church, the Rosary of Black People,
Man kann auch sehen,
there are many Catholic saints, which are very related
dass in der Kirche Igreja do Rosário viele heilige Katholiken gezeigt werden
to syncretic religions of African descent.
die eng mit dem Synkretismus afrikanischer Religionen verbunden sind.
For example, St. Roch is syncretized with Obaluaê deity,
Beispielsweise die Religion São Roque, die mit Obaluaê synkretisierte
St. Barbara with Iansã deity.
Santa Barbara, die sich mit der Iansã-Religion vermischte.
St. anne, with Nanã.
Nossa Senhora de Santana, die mit Nanã verschmolz.
And it's a worship of black saints
Und die Andacht an die heiligen Schwarzen,
which have become symbols of the resistance movements
die zum Symbol des Widerstands
to the population of black slaves.
für die schwarze versklavte Bevölkerung wurden.
Here we have St. Benedict, worshiped
São Benedito,
not only by the black brotherhoods
der nicht nur für die Ordensgemeinschaft ein Bezug ist,
but also in the Congados, feast-day dramatized celebrations.
sondern auch für die Krönungen der Könige.
Here we also have St. George, a very well known saint both to
São Jorge, ein Heiliger, der sehr präsent ist im Katholizismus
popular catholicism and to religions of African descent, such as Umbanda.
und auch in den afrikanischstämmigen Religionen wie Umbanda.